Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5141
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor-Management Committee - Grade Crossing Safety (Box 173, Folder 17)
- Lists, Members (Box 173, Folder 18)
- Los Angeles Harbor Belt Railroad (Box 173, Folder 19)
- National Legislative Representative (Box 173, Folder 20)
- Nevada Car Limit Bill (Box 173, Folder 21)
- Ordinance No. 265, Mendocino County (Box 173, Folder 22)
- Outer Harbor Terminal Railroad (Box 173, Folder 23)
- Physical Exams - Western Pacific Railroad (Box 173, Folder 24)
- Progressive Delegates, 1947 (Box 173, Folder 25)
- Railroad Commission (Box 174, Folder 1-8)
- Railroad Pension Conference (Box 174, Folder 9)
- Railroad Retirement Act (Box 174, Folder 10)
- Southern Pacific Co. (Box 174, Folder 11)
- Wagner Act (Box 174, Folder 12)
- Walks and Handrails (Box 174, Folder 13)
- Western Committee for Railroad Unity (Box 174, Folder 14)
- Western Pacific Railroad (Box 174, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous California documentation (Box 174, Folder 16-17)
- Proceedings of 14th to 25th Biennial Conventions, 1936-1967 (Box 175, Folder 13)
- Minutes, Board. Of Directors, 1901 (Box 175, Folder 12)
- Minutes, Board. Of Directors, 1902-1930 (Box 175, Folder 11)
- Minutes, Board. Of Directors, 1931-1950 (Box 175, Folder 10)
- Legislative Board. Meetings & Board. Of Directors Mtg., 1910-1936 (Box 175, Folder 9)
- Legislative Board Report., 1959-1968 (Box 175, Folder 8)
- Chairman's Reports - v. I-IV (1902-1953) (Box 175, Folder 7)
- Constitution and By-Laws of NYS Legislative Board (Box 175, Folder 6)
- Officers of the Legislative Board, 1910-1914 (Box 175, Folder 5)
- Executive Board - 1901-1909 (Box 175, Folder 1)
- Constitutions, 1928-1942 (Box 175, Folder 2)
- Constitutions, 1917-1926 (Box 175, Folder 3)
- Constitutions, 1901-1915 (Box 175, Folder 4)
- Chairman's Annual Reports, 1902-1967 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  Annual Reports, 1902-1959; Correspondence, 1952-1967
- Financial Records and Reports, 1902-1968 (Box 177, Folder 1)
- Financial Records and Reports, 1902-1968 (Box 178, Folder 1)
- Records of Frank S. Columbus, former Legislative Chairman for the BLF&E (Box 179-185, Folder 1)
  Records donated, processed and listed before remainder of collection was received. This action has been left as processed although scattered throughout the entire N.Y.S. section are also records pertaining to the period when F.S. Columbus was Legislative
- G.D. Morgan, Gen. Chairman - Delaware and Hudson System (Box 180, Folder 10)
- B.L.F. & E. General Council (Box 180, Folder 2)
- Homer Peters, Council Correspondence, 1941-1946 (Box 180, Folder 3)
- Homer Peters, Council Correspondence [cont.], 1941-1946 (Box 180, Folder 4)
- B.L.F.&E. Correspondence - Outside N.Y. State, 1939-1948 (Box 180, Folder 5)
- B.L.F.&E. General Chairman (Box 180, Folder 6)
- W.E. Jones - Correspondence (Box 180, Folder 7)
- Carl J. Goff - Asst. Pres., 1936-1948 (Box 180, Folder 1)
- Albany Convention, 1936 (Box 180, Folder 9)
- D.B. Robertson - President [cont.], 1943-1950 (Box 180, Folder 17)
- Albert Philips - Gen. Secretary-Treasurer, 1931-1941 (Box 180, Folder 11)
- B.L.F.&E. Correspondence, 1937-1942 (Box 180, Folder 12)
- B.L.F.&E. Correspondence [cont.], 1937-1942 (Box 180, Folder 13)
- B.L.F.&E. Correspondence [cont.], 1937-1942 (Box 180, Folder 14)
- D.B. Robertson - President, 1943-1950 (Box 180, Folder 15)
- D.B. Robertson - President [cont.], 1943-1950 (Box 180, Folder 16)
- W.E. Jones - Correspondence [cont.] (Box 180, Folder 8)
- American Railroad Service - Correspondence (Box 181, Folder 10)
- Legislative Board Communications to the BLF&E Members (Box 181, Folder 2)
- Robertson 50th Anniversary. Dinner, Correspondence, 1949 (Box 181, Folder 3)
- Salaried Chairman Proposition (Box 181, Folder 4)
- State & Canadian Legislative Boards, 1930-1941 (Box 181, Folder 5)
- State & Canadian Legislative Boards [cont.], 1930-1941 (Box 181, Folder 6)
- State & Canadian Legislative Boards, 1942-1949 (Box 181, Folder 7)
- Jonas A. McBride - Vice Pres., 1924-1946 (Box 181, Folder 1)
- Controversy, BLF&E-BLE: Printed materials (Box 181, Folder 9)
- Candidate Endorsements A-C (Box 181, Folder 17)
- Controversy between BLF&E and the BLE (Box 181, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, other Railway Brotherhoods, 1942-1950 (Box 181, Folder 12)
- C.R. Dugan - Public Relations Manager, New York Central Systems (Box 181, Folder 13)
- E.S. Duffy - Wabash Railroad (Box 181, Folder 14)
- Railroad Employees Public Relations Association (Box 181, Folder 15)
- Thomas E. Ryan (Box 181, Folder 16)
- State & Canadian Legislative Boards [cont.], 1942-1949 (Box 181, Folder 8)
- Ogden Ross - Caroline O'Day Campaign, 1934 (Box 182, Folder 14)
- Voting Records of Senators & Assemblymen, 1931-1935 (Box 182, Folder 13)
- Voting Records of Senators & Assemblymen, 1920-1930 (Box 182, Folder 12)
- New York State Assembly - Correspondence, 1939-1950 (Box 182, Folder 11)
- Jim Mead's Campaign Committee, 1940 (Box 182, Folder 10)
- Candidate Endorsement - Questions, 1914 (Box 182, Folder 9)
- Candidate Endorsements, Public Service Commissioner 1911 & 1915 (Box 182, Folder 8)
- Candidate Endorsement - Charles. H. Keenan 11/30/1926 (Box 182, Folder 7)
- Candidate Endorsement - Charles. H. Keenan 12/7/1926 (Box 182, Folder 6)
- National Candidates Endorsed, 1924-1936 (Box 182, Folder 5)
- Candidate Endorsements - Candidates for National. Office (Box 182, Folder 4)
- Candidate Endorsements P-W (Box 182, Folder 3)
- Candidate Endorsements D-O [cont.] (Box 182, Folder 2)
- Candidate Endorsements D-O (Box 182, Folder 1)
- Seaway - Addresses by Frank S. Columbus (Box 183, Folder 8)
- Seaway - Federal Power Commission (Box 183, Folder 12)
- Seaway - Eastern Railroad Presidents Conference (Box 183, Folder 11)
- Seaway - Congressional Hearings, 1932-1951 (Box 183, Folder 10)
- Seaway - Congressional Debate, 1941-1952 (Box 183, Folder 9)
- Seaway - BLF&E Publications (Box 183, Folder 8)
- Seaway - Association of American Railroads, Reports, 1947-1954 (Box 183, Folder 8)
- Albany Anti St. Lawrence Conference Committee (Box 183, Folder 1)
- Seaway - Association of American Railroads, Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 183, Folder 9)
- Seaway - Michigan Railroads Association (Box 183, Folder 15)
- New York State Conference In Opposition to the St. Lawrence (Box 183, Folder 7)
- National St. Lawrence Project Conference - Report for (Box 183, Folder 6)
- National St. Lawrence Project Conference: Memoranda, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 5)
- National St. Lawrence Project Conference: McGrath Correspondence, 1947 (Box 183, Folder 4)
- National St. Lawrence Project Conference - McGrath Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 183, Folder 3)
- National St. Lawrence Project Conference - Carroll B. Huntress. Chairman (Box 183, Folder 2)
- Seaway - Association of American Railroads - Publications (Box 183, Folder 10)
- Seaway - Vermont State Railroads Association (Box 183, Folder 22)
- N.Y. State Barge Canal System Tolls (Box 183, Folder 30)
- Motor Trucks - Interstate Cooperative Committee (Box 183, Folder 29)
- Anti-Discrimination Legislation [cont.], 1945 (Box 183, Folder 28)
- Anti-Discrimination Legislation, 1945 (Box 183, Folder 27)
- St. Lawrence Seaway - Resolutions, 1933-1946 (Box 183, Folder 26)
- St. Lawrence Seaway - Resolutions (undated) (Box 183, Folder 25)
- Seaway - General Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 183, Folder 13)
- St. Lawrence Power Development Commission - State of New York, 1941-1954 (Box 183, Folder 23)
- Seaway - Massena, New York (Box 183, Folder 14)
- Seaway - The Maritime Association of the Port of New York (Box 183, Folder 21)
- Seaway - Reports, Notes & Miscellaneous Data (Box 183, Folder 20)
- Seaway - Railroad Co-Operative League of Nations (Box 183, Folder 19)
- Seaway - Publications of Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 183, Folder 18)
- Seaway - Niagara Frontier Planning Board (Box 183, Folder 17)
- Seaway - "New York Waterways" Magazine (Box 183, Folder 16)
- National St. Lawrence Project Conference. - Publications (Box 183, Folder 31)
- St. Lawrence Seaway - News clippings (undated) (Box 183, Folder 24)
- Vestibule Cab Record, 1917-1925 (Box 184, Folder 11)
- Railroad Legislation - Introduced, 1953 (Box 184, Folder 2)
- Savings Bank Life Insurance, 1938-1940 (Box 184, Folder 3)
- Semi-Monthly Pay Bill, 1902-1915 (Box 184, Folder 4)
- Semi-Monthly Pay Bill - Albany Hearings, 1902 (Box 184, Folder 5)
- Semi-Monthly Pay Bill - Albany Hearings, 1909 (Box 184, Folder 6)
- State Legislation, 1912-1927 (Box 184, Folder 7)
- State Legislation, 1912-1927 (Box 184, Folder 8)
- Railroad Legislation - Introduced, 1951 (Box 184, Folder 1)
- State Railroad Laws, 1939 (Box 184, Folder 10)
- Treasury Dept. - War Finance Committee (Box 184, Folder 20)
- Vestibule Cab Law & Court Records, 1917-1936 (Box 184, Folder 12)
- Vestibule Cab (news clipping) March 24, 1918 (Box 184, Folder 13)
- Interstate Commerce Commission Reports, 1940-1950 (Box 184, Folder 14)
- National War Labor Board, 1943-1944 (Box 184, Folder 15)
- Office of Civilian Defense Director - Emergency Transport (Box 184, Folder 16)
- Office of Government Reports (Box 184, Folder 17)
- O.P.A., Labor Office Information Service, 1942-1944 (Box 184, Folder 18)
- Treasury Dept., War Finance Committee, 1941-1943 (Box 184, Folder 19)
- State Legislation, 1927-1930 (Box 184, Folder 9)
- Cornell University - Misc. (Box 185, Folder 11)
- Proposed Student Residence for Cornell Medical College (Box 185, Folder 1)
- Building & Grounds Committee - Architects Reports (Box 185, Folder 2)
- Building & Grounds Committee - Miscellaneous (Box 185, Folder 3)
- Cornell University - Board of Trustees (Box 185, Folder 4)
- Cornell University Correspondence (Box 185, Folder 5)
- Cornell University Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 185, Folder 6)
- Cornell University Correspondence - cont., 1948-1950 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- Cornell University - Correspondence, 1951-1957 (Box 185, Folder 8)
- War Manpower Commission, 1943 (Box 184, Folder 21)
- Cornell University - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Twentieth Century Fund - Correspondence (Box 185, Folder 20)
- Albany Victory War Chest - Correspondence (Box 185, Folder 12)
- Americans for Democratic Action (Box 185, Folder 13)
- Committee to Defend America (Box 185, Folder 14)
- Defense Saving Bond (Box 185, Folder 15)
- New York Labor War Chest (Box 185, Folder 16)
- New York National War Fund (Box 185, Folder 17)
- New York State Citizens' Council, Inc. (Box 185, Folder 18)
- Red Cross War Fund Campaign, 1942 (Box 185, Folder 19)
- Cornell University - Correspondence - cont., 1951-1957 (Box 185, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 186, Folder 1)
- Albany Station, Correspondence re Moving, 1965-1969 (Box 186, Folder 2)
- Albany Rally, 1962 (Box 186, Folder 3)
- Albany Association for the Blind, 1970-1972 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- Association for Western Railways, 1961-1969 (Box 186, Folder 5)
- Baggage Tariff Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 186, Folder 6)
- Barge Canal Bill, 1965-1966 (Box 186, Folder 7)
- Bills (Legislative), 1971 (Box 186, Folder 8-9)
- BLE-ORC-SUNA-BMoW, etc., Correspondence, 1931-1956 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 1959-1971 (Box 187, Folder 2)
- Bryant, R.R., General Secretary-Treasurer, 1959-1965 (Box 187, Folder 3)
- Campaigns of John Bennett and James Mead, 1940-1946 (Box 187, Folder 4-6)
- Canal Tolls, 1935-1940 (Box 187, Folder 7-8)
- Circulars, Official Grand Lodge (scattered Issues), 1953-1967 (Box 187, Folder 9)
- Circulars (old circular letters), 1939-1956 (Box 187, Folder 10)
- Close-Clearance Top of Cars, 1937-1939 (Box 187, Folder 11)
- Coal Slurry Pipeline Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 188, Folder 1)
- Collins, Daniel - SUNA Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 188, Folder 2-3)
- Compulsory Arbitration Law Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 188, Folder 4-5)
- Congressmen Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 188, Folder 6)
- Congressmen, Replies From, 1942-1958 (Box 188, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Cornell University, 1954-1967 (Box 188, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Miscellaneous Grand Lodge Officers, 1924-1964 (Box 188, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1951 (Box 188, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - Columbus, Boardman Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1944-1968 (Box 188, Folder 11-12)
- Correspondence, General, 1959-1971 (Box 189, Folder 1-12)
- Constitution, Amendments, Proposed Legislation, 1936 (Box 189, Folder 13)
- Contract Carrier Buffalo, 1939-1941 (Box 189, Folder 14)
- Convention Information, invitations, replies, resolutions, etc., 1936-1959 (Box 189, Folder 15-19)
- Convention Correspondence (in binders by year), 1942-1952 (Box 190, Folder 1)
- Convention Correspondence (in binder), 1954 (Box 191, Folder 1)
- Convention, 37th and 38th, 1963-1966 (Box 191, Folder 2)
- Convention Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1944-1965 (Box 191, Folder 3-4)
- Drinking Containers, 1949-1962 (Box 191, Folder 5)
- East-West Legislative Comm., 1969-1971 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- Election of Officers by Mall, 1955 (Box 192, Folder 2)
- Elections - Local Lodge, 1961-1968 (Box 192, Folder 3)
- Empire State Union Meeting-Correspondence, 1963 (Box 192, Folder 4)
- Employee's Liability Law-Federal, 1912-1934 (Box 192, Folder 5)
- Endorsements and Contributions, 1968 (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Endorsements - Senate and Assembly, 1970 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- Fair Competition Bills, 1963-1964 (Box 193, Folder 1)
- Featherbedding Practices, 1959 (Box 193, Folder 2)
- Federal Railroad Admin., FBB, 1969-1972 (Box 193, Folder 3)
- Fight For Right, 1965-1967 (Box 193, Folder 4)
- Finance Docket Cases. Misc., 1955-1964 (Box 193, Folder 5)
- Finance Docket Cases, Misc., 1964-1969 (Box 193, Folder 6)
- Fire Insurance Police, Lease, Compensation Ins., 1928-1958 (Box 193, Folder 7)
- First Aid Kit, Letters, 1965-1969 (Box 193, Folder 8-10)
- Flagging Bill, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 1)
- Fraternal Ins. Chap, 783, Laws, 1935-1936 (Box 194, Folder 2)
- Fund Raising, Donation Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 194, Folder 3)
- General Chairman, Correspondence, Misc., 1951-1955 (Box 194, Folder 4)
- Gilbert, H.E., International. President, BLF&E, 1947-1958 (Box 194, Folder 5)
- Gilbert, H.E., International. President, BLF&E, 1951-1954 (Box 194, Folder 6)
- Gilbert, H.E., International. President, BLF&E, 1951-1965 (Box 194, Folder 7)
- Gilbert, H.E., International. President, BLF&E, 1956-1963 (Box 194, Folder 8)
- Grade Crossing Elimination, 1938 (Box 194, Folder 9)
- Health-Welfare Program Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 195, Folder 1)
- Hours of Service Act, Correspondence, 1908-1969 (Box 195, Folder 2-5)
- Insurance Amendments, 1938 (Box 195, Folder 6)
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1959-1968 (Box 195, Folder 7-11)
  Complaints, 1959-62; Correspondence, 1963-68; Train Accident Reports, etc., 1967-68; Violations, 1963-65
- Javits, Jacob K., U.S. Senator, 1968 (Box 195, Folder 12)
- Jerry-Mason Resolution (Box 195, Folder 13)
- Labor Management Improper Practices Act, 1959 (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Labor Paper Correspondence, 1959-1972 (Box 196, Folder 2)
- Ladies' Society, BLF&E, Correspondence, 1930-1970 (Box 196, Folder 3)
- Lampley, A.M., VP, Correspondence, 1947-1965 (Box 196, Folder 4-5)
- Leach, J.A., 1919-1936 (Box 196, Folder 6)
- Legislation, 1931-1969 (Box 196, Folder 7-19)
- Legislative Board - Constitution, 1960 (Box 197, Folder 1)
- Legislative Board - Assessments, Deduction in Salary, etc., 1933 (Box 197, Folder 2)
- Legislative Board - Convention Expenses, 1928-1954 (Box 197, Folder 3)
- Legislative Board - Convention, 1934 (Box 197, Folder 4)
- Legislative Board - History (Box 197, Folder 5)
- Legislative and Education Conferences, 1961 (Box 197, Folder 6)
- Legislative Session, 1961-1968 (Box 197, Folder 7-14)
- Lodge 1, Port Jervis, 1902-1958 (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
- Lodge 12, Buffalo, 1903-1958 (Box 198, Folder 3-4)
- Lodge 71, 0neonta, 1903-1964 (Box 198, Folder 5-6)
- Lodge 74, Mechanicville, 1902-1964 (Box 198, Folder 7-8)
- Lodge 85, Buffalo, 1903-1964 (Box 198, Folder 9-10)
- Lodge 92, Oswego, 1901-1964 (Box 198, Folder 11-12)
- Lodge 99, Rochester, 1902-1964 (Box 198, Folder 13-18)
- Lodge 101, Buffalo, 1902-1964 (Box 199, Folder 1-2)
- Lodge 120, Syracuse, 1901-1964 (Box 199, Folder 3-5)
- Lodge 121, Corning, 1902-1964 (Box 199, Folder 6-7)
- Lodge 149, New York City, 1903-1948 (Box 199, Folder 8)
- Lodge 155, New York City, 1911-1941 (Box 199, Folder 9)
- Local 169, Hornell, 1903-1964 (Box 199, Folder 10-11)
- Lodge 180, Plattsburgh, 1902-1922 (Box 199, Folder 12)
- Lodge 209, Whitehall, 1912-1964 (Box 199, Folder 13-14)
- Lodge 210, Schenectady, 1902-1959 (Box 199, Folder 15-16)
- Lodge 212, Watertown, 1903-1956 (Box 199, Folder 17)
- Lodge 213, Syracuse, 1903-1961 (Box 199, Folder 18-19)
- Lodge 215, Watervliet, 1902-1958 (Box 199, Folder 20)
- Lodge 216, Norwich, 1902-1957 (Box 199, Folder 21)
- Lodge 227, Binghamton, 1910-1964 (Box 199, Folder 22-25)
- Lodge 229, Utica, 1902-1964 (Box 200, Folder 1-2)
- Lodge 230, Albany, 1902-1964 (Box 200, Folder 3-4)
- Lodge 232, Middletown, 1901-1958 (Box 200, Folder 5)
- Lodge 241, Buffalo, 1902-1964 (Box 200, Folder 6-7)
- Lodge 242, Elmira, 1903-1960 (Box 200, Folder 8-10)
- Lodge 276, Buffalo, 1905-1964 (Box 200, Folder 11-12)
- Lodge 291, Malverne, 1902-1947 (Box 200, Folder 13)
- Lodge 309, Richmond Hill, 1903-1964 (Box 200, Folder 14-15)
- Lodge 315, Watervliet, 1902-1964 (Box 200, Folder 16-17)
- Lodge 316, Buffalo, 1902-1970 (Box 200, Folder 18-20)
- Lodge 320, Avon, 1915-1948 (Box 201, Folder 1)
- Lodge 326, Salamanca, 1934-1955 (Box 201, Folder 2)
- Lodge 334, Syracuse, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 3-4)
- Lodge 339, Clifton, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 5-6)
- Lodge 362, Niagara Falls, 1907-1964 (Box 201, Folder 7-8)
- Lodge 363, New York City, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 9-10)
- Lodge 398, Olean, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 11)
- Lodge 463, Elmira, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 12-13)
- Lodge 472, Buffalo, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 14-15)
- Lodge 475, St. Allans, 1937-1941 (Box 201, Folder 16)
- Lodge 509, Syracuse, 1902-1964 (Box 201, Folder 17-18)
- Lodge 524, Ogdensburg, 1907-1918 (Box 201, Folder 19)
- Lodge 614, Buffalo, 1903-1964 (Box 201, Folder 20-21)
- Lodge 666, New York City, 1905-1964 (Box 201, Folder 22-23)
- Lodge 668, Lackawanna, 1907-1964 (Box 201, Folder 24-25)
- Lodge 681, Salamanca, 1910-1964 (Box 202, Folder 1-2)
- Lodge 699, Albany, 1907-1961 (Box 202, Folder 3)
- Lodge 700, Port Jervis, 1915-1964 (Box 202, Folder 4-5)
- Lodge 708, Albany, 1910-1964 (Box 202, Folder 6-7)
- Lodge 732, Saratoga Springs, 1915-1958 (Box 202, Folder 8)
- Lodge 765, Kingston, 1913-1964 (Box 202, Folder 9)
- Lodge 777, Warwick, 1915-1964 (Box 202, Folder 10)
- Lodge 790, Maybrook, 1915-1964 (Box 202, Folder 11)
- Lodge 807, Auburn, 1914-1970 (Box 202, Folder 12)
- Lodge 809, Rensselaer, 1939-1964 (Box 202, Folder 13)
- Lodge 836, Hornell, 1914-1964 (Box 202, Folder 14)
- Lodge 876, Utica, 1926-1964 (Box 202, Folder 15)
- Lodge 880, Terrytown, 1920-1964 (Box 202, Folder 16)
- Lodge 940, Binghamton, 1942-1964 (Box 202, Folder 17)
- Lodge 952, Manchester, 1944-1964 (Box 202, Folder 18)
- Lodge 975, Buffalo, 1949-1964 (Box 202, Folder 19)
- Lodge Suspension Notices, 1960-1968 (Box 202, Folder 20)
- Maddren, William, ORC, Correspondence, 1930-1961 (Box 203, Folder 1)
- Mahoney's Dinner, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 203, Folder 2)
- Mass Transit Bond, $2 1/2 Billion, 1967 (Box 203, Folder 3)
- Medicare Bill, Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 203, Folder 4)
- Members, BLF&E (Box 203, Folder 5)
- Metroliner Service, Washington and New York, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 6)
- Midcap, W.C., Editor and Manager, 1959-1969 (Box 203, Folder 7-8)
- Miscellaneous Meetings, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 9)
- Motor Truck and Bus Legislation, 1933-1938 (Box 203, Folder 10-13)
- Negro Problem, 1946 (Box 203, Folder 13a)
- NYC Lines E. Civil Action, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 14)
- NY Fraternal Congress, 1970-1971 (Box 203, Folder 15)
- New York-New Jersey States Meeting, 1929-1969 (Box 203, Folder 16)
- New York State Barge Canal Correspondence, 1959-1967 (Box 203, Folder 17-16)
- New York State Conference of Mayors, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 19)
- New York State Board of Directors, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 204, Folder 1)
- New York State Conference of Mayors, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 204, Folder 2)
- News-Gram, 1960-1965 (Box 204, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings Relative to Work Rules Dispute, Threatened Strike, Legislation, etc., 1963 (Box 204, Folder 4)
- No-Fault Insurance, 1970-1971 (Box 204, Folder 5-6)
- Officers, Election of, 1970-1971 (Box 204, Folder 7)
- Ohio Legislative Board, 1963-1965 (Box 204, Folder 8)
- Pennsylvania Legislative Board, 1960-1965 (Box 204, Folder 9)
- Perlman-Mahoney, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 204, Folder 10)
- Peters, Homer, FBB Meeting re Legislation, 1970 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Peters, Homer, Speech Before Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 2)
- Peters, Homer, Counsel, 1943-1956 (Box 205, Folder 3)
- Peru Railroad Workers, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 4)
- Political Correspondence, 1954-1968 (Box 205, Folder 5-7)
- Political Endorsement, 1962-1964 (Box 205, Folder 9-9)
- Power Brake Law, Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 205, Folder 10)
- Presidential Study Commissions, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 11)
- President's Conference, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 205, Folder 12)
- Primary Endorsements, etc., 1960-1962 (Box 206, Folder 3)
- Railway Labor Executives Association (Box 206, Folder 18)
- Public Service Commission Correspondence (Box 206, Folder 7)
- Public Service Commission Correspondence (Box 206, Folder 8)
- Public Service Commission Correspondence (Box 206, Folder 9)
- Railroad Retirement Act, 1932-1969 (Box 206, Folder 12)
- Railroad Retirement Board (Box 206, Folder 14)
- Railroad Retirement Forms for GL (Box 206, Folder 16)
- Primary Contest Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Primary Endorsements, etc., 1960-1962 (Box 206, Folder 2)
- Primary Race, 1970 (Box 206, Folder 4)
- Protective Measures Bill, 1966 (Box 206, Folder 5)
- Public Service Commission, Calendar Hearings; Correspondence, 1907-1970 (Box 206, Folder 6)
- Railroad Annual Meetings, Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 206, Folder 10)
- Railroad Retirement Act, 1932-1969 (Box 206, Folder 11)
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1937-1959 (Box 206, Folder 13)
- Railroad Retirement Forms, 1937-1958 (Box 206, Folder 15)
- Railway Labor Executive's Association, 1963-1967 (Box 206, Folder 17)
- Railway Labor Political League, 1960-1968 (Box 207, Folder 1-5)
- Resolutions, Memorials, 1928-1954 (Box 207, Folder 6)
- Rockefeller, Governor - Task Force to Evaluate Effect of PC Bankruptcy on Local Government, 1970-1971 (Box 207, Folder 7)
- Roosevelt, F.D., Resolutions, Campaign Literature, etc., 1924-1939 (Box 207, Folder 8)
- Safety Award Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 208, Folder 2)
- State and Canadian Legislative Board, 1959-1971 (Box 208, Folder 11)
- Safety Awards, Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 208, Folder 1-2)
- Salamanca Drinking Water Case, 1933-1936 (Box 208, Folder 3)
- Samuels, Howard, 1965 (Box 208, Folder 4)
- Service and Compensation Railroad Retirement Board., 1938-1945 (Box 208, Folder 5)
- Sixtieth Anniversary Correspondence, 1961 (Box 208, Folder 6)
- Sixty-Fifth Anniversary Correspondence, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 7)
- Social Security Act, 1937 (Box 208, Folder 8)
- Southern Union Meeting, 1963 (Box 208, Folder 9)
- State and Canadian Legislative Board, 1959-1971 (Box 208, Folder 10-11)
- State Assemblymen, Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 208, Folder 12)
- State Senators Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 208, Folder 13)
- State Union Meeting, 1932 (Box 208, Folder 14)
  Vote of Lodges re Meeting
- Strike Information, 1963 (Box 208, Folder 15)
- Sympathy Resolutions, 1932-1936 (Box 208, Folder 16)
- Testimonial Dinners, etc., 1968-1969 (Box 209, Folder 1)
- Texas National Convention, 1968 (Box 209, Folder 2)